sociamonials.com 2015-04-19

# Sociamonials - Capture and syndicate your customer's passion

Your privacy matters to us. We promise to respect your contact preferences and to guard your private information. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**What Personally Identifying Information Does Sociamonials Collect?**

The level of information Sociamonials collect depends on the level of your use. If you sign up to be a registered user of Sociamonials, we collect your email address, full name, address and credit card information. You can change your information by going to your “My Account” page (you must be logged in to view this page). We use SSL encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.

For your protection, Sociamonials partners with a secure payment gateway to provide a safe, secure payment procedure.

Sociamonials uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

**Sociamonials does not share your email address or other personally identifying information with any third parties** , except our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

**What Tracking Information Does Sociamonials Collect?**

Your browser installs a cookie on your computer when you visit our site. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies facilitate access to our website and personalize your online experience.

We use cookies to record current session information, encrypted users’ login information, provide services, and compile analytics about our users.

In addition, our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users’ movements around our site and understand trends.

Sociamonials uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, enforce our Terms of Use, and research.

**How We Store our Data**

Sociamonials uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run Sociamonials. The technical processing and transmission of the Service, including your content, may involve (a) transmissions over various networks, and (b) changes to conform and adapt to technical requirements of connecting networks or devices.

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.

**When We Will Disclose our Data**

Sociamonials may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas, warrants, other valid legal processes, or when your actions violate the Terms of Service. In addition, Sociamonials may disclose certain information to our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.

**Email Contact**

Sociamonials does not share your email information with third parties, except our service providers, such as credit-card payment processors, performing services on our behalf. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purposes.

If you sign up for an account, Sociamonials collects your email address. We may occasionally use this email to contact you for site-related issues. If you do not want us to contact you for commercial purposes, you may unsubscribe using the link in any of our commercial emails. Sociamonials complies with the Federal Can-Spam Act (15 U.S.C. 7701 et seq.).

We need your help in discovering illegal or inappropriate email conduct perpetrated by impostors. In the event that you receive an email that you feel is spam and it appears to be sent by or affiliated with Sociamonials, please forward the email to support@sociamonials.com.

**Visiting Our Website From Outside the U.S.**

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those service providers with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.

**Refund Policy**

This refund policy only applies to online purchases. If a separate written agreement governs your relationship with Sociamonials, that document will specify the refund policy. You may obtain a refund for any online purchases within 7 days of purchase for any reason.
